Greetings, fellow space citizens. I'm Jim Cooper.
问候 太空公民朋友们 我是吉姆-库珀
I'm here today as a member of AGI's ComSpOC corporation
今天我作为AGI的ComSpOC公司的成员来到这里
and I'll be bringing to you today our latest spacecast.
今天我将为大家带来我们最新的太空广播
We're trying something a little bit different today.
我们今天正在尝试一些不同的东西
This is our first time that we're going to do a one-man show.
这是我们第一次做一个人的节目
I'm here in the studio by myself essentially
我在演播室里基本上是一个人
and not going to be interviewed or anything.
不接受采访或任何东西
I'll just be talking with you guys through this.
我只是通过这个和你们交谈
Essentially we're going to be talking about large constellations
从本质上讲 我们要讨论的是大型星座
the new large constellations of satellites that are coming.
即将到来的新的大型卫星星座
But it'll be just me today.
但今天只有我一个人
And we'll see how that works out for a new format for our spacecast.
我们将看看这对我们的空间广播的新形式有什么作用
As I said I want to talk to you guys a little bit today about what's going on large constellations of satellites.
正如我所说 我今天想和你们谈一谈大型卫星星座的情况
I know this something that's been in the news a lot over the last year or two
我知道在过去的一两年里 这个东西在新闻中出现了很多次
and we just kind of want to address some of the things that we're seeing here from our perspective
我们只是想从我们的角度谈谈我们在这里看到的一些事情
and some of the analysis that we do.
以及我们所做的一些分析
Now we've done some of this before.
现在我们已经做了一些这样的事情
I know that we presented in the past
我知道 我们在过去提出
where we've shown various videos of debris clouds and LEO
我们已经展示了各种碎片云和低地轨道的视频
and debris clouds in GEO and we've even done large constellations in the past.
和地球同步轨道的碎片云 我们甚至在过去做了大型的星座
But of course those are being routinely and regularly updated.
但当然 这些都是例行的 定期更新的
As more companies jump into the space game, they want to get a piece of the action
随着越来越多的公司跳入太空游戏 他们想在行动中分一杯羹
so to speak they've got new and innovative and entrepreneurial ideas.
可以说 他们有新的、创新的和创业的想法
And so they're creating these new concepts
因此 他们正在创造这些新概念
and as they create these new concepts and begin the design and start to move down the path
当他们创造这些新概念并开始设计并开始往下走的时候
of course they have to file for being able to launch those satellites into space.
当然 他们必须提出申请 以便能够将这些卫星发射到太空
So what I want to show you here is essentially a video
因此 我想在这里向你展示的基本上是一个视频
that we've done a version of this has been done in the past
我们已经做了一个版本 在过去已经做过了
but we're doing it now is redoing the video
但我们现在做的是重做这段视频
to kind of show you what the latest filings look like.
向你们展示最新的文件是什么样子的
We'll go ahead and bring that video up right now.
我们现在就去把这个视频拿出来
And this is our latest large constellation video
这是我们最新的大型星座视频
and you'll see what's going to happen here.
你会看到这里将发生什么
This video is going to populate by year over on the left
这段视频将按年份在左边弹出
with the number of satellites in these various constellations by these companies that are going up each year.
这些公司在这些不同的星座中的卫星数量 每年都在增加
You can kind of see those numbers grow
你可以看到这些数字的增长
and how drastic that they get as you move through the course of the next decade.
以及它们在未来十年的过程中变得多么急剧
And of course this includes things like the SpaceX Starlink constellation
当然 这包括像SpaceX的Starlink星座的东西
the OneWeb satellites which are here listed in the world view
OneWeb卫星 这些卫星在这里被列在世界视图中
the boeing satellites amazon and everything.
波音卫星亚马逊和所有东西
Recently the last time we did this video
最近 我们上次做这个视频时
these numbers reflected something in the neighborhood if I remember right 48000 or 50000.
这些数字反映了在附近的东西 如果我记得没错的话 是48000或50000
What you're seeing now is a drastic increase
你现在看到的是一个急剧的增长
and we're actually looking at over a hundred thousand satellites
我们实际上看到的是超过十万颗的卫星
that are supposed to be launched over the next decade.
在未来的十年里 应该会有超过十万颗卫星被发射
right from now through the year 2029.
从现在到2029年
And you can kind of see as that video builds out right there and what that looks like.
你可以看到这段视频的内容 以及它的样子
Now to be sure the video I just showed you is for public filing.
现在要确定的是 我刚才给你看的视频是公开的
So we don't really know again
所以我们并不真正知道
which of these are going to actually succeed
其中哪些是要真正成功
to being operational flight-capable and end up operating as constellations.
成为可运行的飞行能力 并最终作为星座运行
However even any substantial amount of these that makes it, if it's 20% 30% 50%
然而 即使是任何大量的这些使它 如果它是20% 30% 50%
give it some number if it's a substantial percentage of all those satellites
给它一些数字 如果它是所有这些卫星的一个相当大的百分比
that's going to obviously represent a sea change or I don't know a space change maybe is a better term here
这显然将代表一个巨大的变化 或者我不知道一个空间的变化 也许是一个更好的术语在这里
in the actual operational environment today
在今天的实际操作环境中
and the concerns that we have today as a result of this burgeoning space population.
以及我们今天由于这个不断增长的空间人口而产生的担忧
Now since I'm the only one in the studio today and there's nobody here to do this,
现在 由于我是今天演播室里唯一的人 而且这里没有人做这个
I'm gonna go ahead and ask myself a question.
我将继续前进 并问自己一个问题
Well Jim that's interesting that was a lot of dots on that screen.
嗯 吉姆 这很有趣 屏幕上有很多点
What does that all mean?
这都是什么意思？
Jim that's a fantastic question.
吉姆 这是一个奇妙的问题
That's a great question.
这是个好问题
Let me show you what that means right now.
现在让我给你看看这意味着什么
I want to bring up a slide here.
我想在这里调出一张幻灯片
This is something we've also done in the past of
这是我们过去也做过的事情
sort of doing an assessment of what all of those dots look like.
对所有这些点是什么样子的进行评估
And what we're doing is we're now re-doing this.
而我们正在做的是我们现在重新做这个
We've done this assessment all over again
我们已经重新做了这个评估
to account for the increased numbers that are reflected in that video that you've just seen
考虑到你们刚才看到的视频中所反映的数字的增加
and so I want to run through this.
所以我想通过这个
This is kind of a numbers chart
这是个数字图表
but when you really dig into the numbers it's alarming.
但当你真正深入了解这些数字时 它是令人震惊的
It's eye-opening to say the least.
至少可以说是大开眼界
And again I know we've done this before but I'll do it for you here again.
我知道我们之前已经做过了 但我还是要在这里为你们做一遍
I'm just going to grab one particular constellation of satellites.
我只是要抓住一个特定的卫星星座
Let's look at the SpaceX M-T segment there
让我们看一下SpaceX的M-T部分
which is going to have 20940 spacecraft operating in that area right there
它将有20940个航天器在该地区运行 就在那里
and what we've done is
而我们所做的是
we've looked at the encounter rates for that group of satellites in today's current resident space object catalog.
我们所做的是 在今天的常驻空间物体目录中 我们已经看了这组卫星的相遇率
So that RSO number is what you see right here at the top
因此 RSO的数字是你在这里看到的 就在顶部
that reflects the catalog as it exists today under today's sort of global capabilities
它反映了在今天的全球能力下存在的目录
which are essentially tracking and maintaining objects down to about 10 centimeters in LEO
这基本上是跟踪和维护低地球轨道上大约10厘米的物体
where the SpaceX Starlink constellation will be.
SpaceX的Starlink星座将在那里
And if you look at that encounter rate.
而如果你看一下这个相遇率
What you can see is that there is a chance if you look at the collisions over the next 10 year period
你可以看到的是 如果你看一下未来10年内的碰撞 有可能
they're going to have essentially 43 collisions actual things colliding coming together in space
他们基本上会有43次碰撞 实际的东西在太空中碰撞在一起
with that constellation operating inside today's current RSO catalog of objects that's up there.
与该星座在今天的RSO天体目录内运作 这是在那里
Analogous to that if they decide for operational purposes
与此类似 如果他们决定出于操作目的
that they want to receive a warning anytime something comes within three km of one of their satellites
他们想在任何时候收到警告 只要有东西进入他们的一个卫星的三公里之内
they're going to receive over 13 almost 14 million warnings in this 10-year period.
在这10年期间 他们将收到超过1300-1400万个警告
And if we take that a step further and they decide again just for operational purposes
如果我们更进一步 他们再次决定只是为了操作的目的
that they want to maneuver whenever anything approaches within one kilometer of one of these satellites
只要有东西接近这些卫星之一的一公里范围内 他们就想进行机动操作
they're going to have to perform a million and a half collision avoidance maneuvers.
他们将不得不进行一百五十万次避免碰撞的演习
Now that's already operationally untenable from an operation standpoint.
现在 从操作的角度来看 这在操作上已经是站不住脚了
If you are continuing to use today's standards and today's processes for space flight safety
如果你继续使用今天的标准和今天的太空飞行安全程序
it's kind of a heads up warning if you will.
这是一种警告 如果你愿意的话
And it's already kind of operationally untenable from that standpoint.
而且从这个角度来看 它在操作上已经有点站不住脚了
If we carry that to the next step over on the right side of this chart
如果我们把它带到下一步 在这个图表的右边
and you look at a RSO resident space object catalog of 200000 or more.
你看一下200000个或更多的RSO常驻空间物体目录
Now this would reflect some of the newer capabilities that are coming online.
现在这将反映出一些正在上线的较新能力
Some of the commercial capabilities, military capabilities like the new US Space Force Space Fence Radar
一些商业能力 军事能力 如新的美国空军空间栅栏雷达
which is tracking small debris down into the single centimeter.
它可以追踪小到一厘米的小碎片
Not one centimeter but single digit if you will.
不是一厘米 而是个位数 如果你愿意的话
Somewhere around one two three four five something like that centimeter size targets.
大约在一二三四五这样的厘米大小的目标
You're going to see this catalog that's currently up there today of objects go up.
你将会看到这个目录 目前在那里的物体上升了
These are all the satellites that are there today we're just not tracking or haven't tracked them in the past
这些都是今天在那里的卫星 我们只是没有跟踪或者过去没有跟踪它们
because the capabilities weren't there.
因为能力不在那里
But in the future they will they're starting to come online right now.
但在未来 他们会的 他们现在就开始上线了
So we're already going to see the catalog grow.
所以我们已经要看到目录的增长
And so if we now compare the Starlink constellation that we referenced
因此 如果我们现在比较一下我们所提到的星联星座
with this new currently existing catalog expanded to account for all that small debris
与这个新的目前存在的目录进行比较 以考虑到所有的小碎片
you see what those new numbers look like.
你可以看到这些新的数字是什么样子的
We're upwards of 400 collisions over a 10-year period with one of those pieces of debris
我们在10年的时间里与这些碎片中的一个发生了400次以上的碰撞
157 million warnings and 17 million plus maneuvers to avoid collisions right.
1.57亿次警告和1700多万次机动以避免碰撞 对吗？
So obviously that's all operationally untenable
所以显然这在操作上是站不住脚的
and what that's driving really is the need for better space flight safety.
而这也促使我们需要更好的太空飞行安全
Essentially building up a regime for space traffic management
从本质上说 建立一个空间交通管理的制度
and from a technical standpoint
而且从技术角度来看
that's going to drive the need for things like advanced analytics, comprehensive data fusion
这将推动对高级分析、综合数据融合等事物的需求
to be able to essentially automatically
以便能够在本质上自动
ingest and process data across all formats and phenomenologies and standards
摄取和处理所有格式、现象和标准的数据
so that you can work with all the authoritative data that's out there
这样 你就可以使用所有的权威数据了
and realistic error portrayals.
和现实的错误描述
You need this stuff so that you can essentially make correct
你需要这些东西 这样你就可以从本质上做出正确的
essentially informed with decision quality information.
基本上是用决策质量的信息来告知
You can make informed decisions on whether or not to maneuver.
你可以在是否进行机动的问题上做出明智的决定
Obviously when you maneuver you're expending fuel.
很明显 当你机动时 你在消耗燃料
You are coming off a particular operation or customer support.
你正从一个特定的操作或客户支持中走出来
There are reasons that you don't want to maneuver
有一些原因 你不希望操纵
and you only want to maneuver when you really have to for space flight safety.
而且你只想在你真的需要时进行机动 以保证空间飞行安全
So we need to bring some of these new capabilities on board
因此 我们需要把这些新的能力带到船上去
to deal with that and to provide that level of decision quality information
来处理这个问题 并提供这种水平的决策质量信息
to make well-informed decisions for space flight safety purposes.
以便为太空飞行安全目的做出明智的决定
Now of course the US from a governmental standpoint has recognized this two years ago.
当然 美国从政府的角度已经在两年前认识到这一点
Now they released SPD-3, Space Policy Document number 3
现在他们发布了SPD-3 空间政策文件编号3
which dealt with space traffic management.
其中涉及到空间交通管理
At the time SPD-3 assigned from a writ large standpoint.
当时SPD-3从一个大的角度分配
There are numerous roles and responsibilities across the board
从运营和管理的角度来看 有许多角色和责任 贯穿始终
from an operations standpoint and management standpoint.
从操作的角度和管理的角度
Some things on research and development, international cooperation and everything
一些关于研究和发展的事情 国际合作和一切
but writ large writ SPD-3 at the time assigned the main responsibility for this
但是 SPD-3在当时把主要的责任分配给了太空商业办公室
to the office of Space Commerce in the Department of Commerce.
到商业部的空间商业办公室
Last year to become more informed on this.
去年 为了更多了解这方面的情况
Of course congress commissioned the National Academy of Public Administration to perform a study
当然 国会委托国家公共管理学院进行了一项研究
to look at space traffic management from a rules and responsibilities standpoint
从规则和责任的角度看空间交通管理
and from an organizational standpoint to best understand where that should go
并从组织的角度 以最好地了解应该去哪里
and that study was made public last week.
该研究报告上周被公开了
And they confirmed that probably, not probably.
他们证实 可能 不是可能
They confirmed that office of Space Commerce is probably
他们证实 空间商业办公室可能是
the most correct or most appropriate organization to take this on
最正确或最合适的组织来承担这个任务
given the factors that they looked at.
鉴于他们研究的因素
So that seems to back up what SPD-3 said.
所以这似乎支持了SPD-3的说法
They also noted in their study that this is a critical capability that we need to move out on without delay.
他们在研究中还指出 这是一种关键能力 我们需要毫不拖延地推进
And we all agree with that.
我们都同意这一点
Here at AGI ComSpOC corporation we're hoping as responsible space operators.
在AGI ComSpOC公司 我们希望作为负责任的空间运营商
Everybody else agrees with that as well.
其他所有人也都同意这一点
There seems to be a burgeoning discussion on this.
关于这个问题似乎有一个蓬勃发展的讨论
One that has kind of moved past the idea that this is a problem.
一种已经超越了这是一个问题的想法
I think it's accepted as a problem.
我认为它被认为是一个问题
And the conversation is now moved into what do we do about the problem.
现在的对话已经转移到我们该如何处理这个问题
How do we implement solutions.
我们如何实施解决方案
And that's a good place to be and that's where we need to continue to take this.
这是一个很好的地方 这也是我们需要继续努力的地方
So with all of that that kind of brings you guys all up to speed here on where we are.
因此 所有这些都使你们了解了我们的情况
This is obviously a dynamic situation.
这显然是一个动态的情况
I'm sure it's going to continue to unfold.
我相信它将会继续发展
There's going to continue to be entrepreneurial efforts out there.
将继续有创业的努力在那里
New ideas, new concepts. That's all great stuff.
新的想法 新的概念 这都是很好的东西
That's what we want.
这就是我们想要的
That's great for space, great for all you know world economies and everything like that.
这对空间很好 对所有你知道的世界经济和类似的一切都很好
so we want to see that continue.
所以我们希望看到这种情况继续下去
What that's going to mean obviously these numbers are going to change over time even more.
这将意味着 显然这些数字将随着时间的推移发生更大的变化
And when that happens
而当这种情况发生时
I'm sure we'll be coming back to you with updated information, updated videos, updated assessments.
我相信我们会向你们提供更新的信息 更新的视频 更新的评估
We'll continue to keep you guys up to speed on all of that.
我们将继续让你们了解所有这些的最新情况
And with that I think that's all of the information that we've got to broadcast to you today.
我想这就是我们今天要向你们广播的所有信息
We thank you for joining us.
我们感谢你加入我们
We hope you enjoyed the new format here.
我们希望你喜欢这里的新形式
And with that we will sign off.
在此 我们将宣布结束
Take care everybody.
大家保重
Have a wonderful space day.
有一个美好的太空日
The end.
结束